This rock is reserved for me, Almighty
Naruto, the fifth hokage!
Naruto again?
Up with the stupid pranks!
Looks like he drew his own face this time.
Now that disrespectful
little... Look at that.
I can't believe they let him graduate from
the academy.
Our hidden lead ninja have really gone
downhill.
Is he okay?
I mean, think about what he is.
Don't even go there.
Oops.
Sorry.
Ah, shut up already!
What are you doing?
How big a fool are you?
Hey, Iruka-sensei!
Naruto, you just graduated.
Why would you do that?
Well, I thought it was a nice way to
commemorate my graduation, you know?
You erase all of that graffiti right now!
And that's it!
I'm going!
Unbelievable.
You're about to become a genin,
you know?
I'm worried about your future.
This is the last day you'll have to worry
about me, Iruka-sensei!
Huh?
Check this out!
From now on, I'm gonna work my butt off to
become Hokage!
And I'm gonna surpass all the Hokage
before me!
Naruto...
What are you talking about?
Becoming Hokage is not as easy as you
think.
Just watch me, Iruka-sensei!
Where does all that confidence come from?
I'm gonna work my butt off!
You'll see!
Good grief...
To be continued... Come on!
I'm going to chase you away And I'm in a
hurry My dried-up heart Has to be at home
To see you A little pause... and we are
back.
A little pause... and we are back.
Listen, kid.
You sure you want me to take your picture
like that?
Just do it!
Come on already!
Come on!
Don't blame me later.
Say cheese!
Cheese!
At first, you know, I couldn't figure out
exactly how to do it.
It took me like three hours to work it out
and stuff.
But, finally, I got it.
Like, an art project on my face.
Only cooler.
Take it again.
No way!
We can't accept this photo.
Yeah?
Well, I'm not doing it again!
Transform!
Pretty please, Lord Hook.
Okay.
That's the sexy jutsu you say?
Very tricky.
Much too tricky.
Don't do it again.
And where is your headband, Naruto.
You're supposed to be wearing it.
Oh, I'm not putting it on until the
orientation.
I don't want to get hurt.
So, you want your headband
nice, but your photo, which
is supposed to identify you,
makes you look like a clown.
It's for ninja training and missions,
which is the key to your future.
Look at this picture, you can't even tell
who it is!
Well, fine!
How am I supposed to know all this
complicated stuff anyway?
Old man!
I challenge you!
I'm going to defeat you and become the
best hokage!
Ow!
My grandson, another headache.
Something tripped me!
Are you okay, honorable grandson?
And by the way, there's nothing here for
you to trip on, it's pretty flat.
Who is this shrimp?
It's that kid!
Alright, you're the one who tripped me,
aren't you?
You tripped over your own feet,
dork!
Hey, you!
Take your hands off of him!
Right now!
He's the honorable grandson of the
honorable third hokage!
That stopped him, just like all the rest.
Now that he knows who I am, he won't dare
lay a finger on me.
What's the matter, huh?
I thought you were going to hit me,
tough guy!
Afraid because the third hokage is my
grandfather?
I don't care if it's your grandmother!
So believe it!
Ah!
This is not looking good.
I know that you're following me,
so just give it up!
Saw through my disguise, huh?
The rumors about you are true,
you're good!
Alright, I'll be your apprentice and
you'll be my trainer!
Huh?
And afterward, you've
got to show me how to do
that sexy jutsu thing you
did on Grandpa Hokage!
This is some kind of joke, isn't it?
No, I need a new trainer!
Please, boss!
Huh?
Boss?
Yeah, you're the boss!
Boss, boss, boss!
Well, how can I refuse?
Where'd he go now?
I think he followed Naruto, but I've no
idea where they're going.
He's with Naruto?
That's a disaster!
Honorable Grandson!
Naruto?
What has he done with the Honorable
Grandson?
Hmm?
What's his evil plan?
Where did they go?
I am a Jōnin, the highest ninja level,
and I'm an official.
I'm the elite trainer of future Hokage.
Any parasite that leeches onto my student
will be squashed!
So, what's up with this obsession you've
got with your grandfather?
My grandfather named me Konohamaru.
After the ancient name of the village.
So it should be easy to remember.
But no one calls me that name.
Not one person in the whole village.
That's because when they look at me,
they don't really see me.
All they see is the Honorable Grandson of
the Lord Hokage.
No one knows who I am.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's like I'm invisible.
Like I don't exist.
I hate that.
That's the reason I've got to become a
Hokage now so people know who I am.
Get real.
You think people are going to accept a
squirt like you?
A kid can't just turn into a Hokage after
a day or two.
What?
It's not that simple.
You keep saying Hokage, Hokage.
To really be a Hokage, you know what
you'll have to do?
What?
What is it?
You're going to have to defeat me in
battle!
I found you!
The nine-tailed fox.
That icy stare.
They all look at me that way.
So, Honorable Grandson, time to go home.
No way!
I'm learning how to beat my grandfather so
I can get the title.
Hokage!
Now don't get in my way!
A Hokage is more than just a fighter.
He must know virtue, honor, wisdom,
and he must be skilled at a thousand jutsu.
You don't even know one jutsu.
Transform!
Hi there.
Like my jutsu?
Hey, he's not defeated.
What?
What kind of scandalous technique is that?
Such tasteless vulgarity can never
influence me.
I am far above it.
Honorable Grandson, stop this.
Right now!
Naruto's turning you into a delinquent.
Only my special training can put you on
the fast track to becoming a Hokage!
Just leave me alone!
Shadow clone jutsu!
Whoa!
This is unreal!
Hmph.
I'm not impressed.
I'm a jonin, an elite ninja warrior.
I'm not some lightweight like Mizu.
Watch how a real ninja defeats an upstart!
Come on, boss!
Ready?
Transform!
Oh...
Nice to meet you!
AHHHHHH!!!
Gotcha!
With my harem jutsu!
He's combined shadow cloning with his own
invention, the sexy jutsu.
What a foolish ninja technique.
And he could probably get me with it too.
Oh man!
I couldn't even beat that snobby trainer
of mine!
I want to be Hokage so bad, but I keep
messing up!
Why can't I do it?
You really think it's that easy?
To be a Hokage, you have to be the
greatest of all ninjas.
You have to prove yourself so everyone
believes in you.
Look at me!
I've been through a lot already.
I've been ignored, pushed away, and
treated like I had the plague or something.
And after all that, I found one person who
believes in me.
To find that one person, I had to get
knocked down a lot.
So you better make sure that you're ready.
For what?
For lots of sweat.
And tears.
While you're learning to be a ninja.
By the way, there is no easy way to
becoming Hokage.
Believe it.
Ha!
Who do you think you are anyway,
giving me a big lecture like that?
That's it.
I'm not going to be your apprentice
anymore.
From now on, we're rivals.
Well, I can't be your trainer anyway.
Because tomorrow, I start my advanced
ninja studies.
But I accept your challenge.
And someday, we'll fight for the title of
Lord Hokage.
So let's both look forward to that day,
Konohamaru.
...
At last, he's finally started down the
path to becoming a true ninja.
... ...
But those two are five years apart in age.
Lady Hanabi's amazing.
How did your training go today,
Lady Hanabi?
It was the same as usual.
You seem really sad.
But you've had so much fun with it before
today.
Yeah.
After observing for a
while, I believe it will be hard
to let Hinata take over
as head of the main family.
A decision will have to be made soon.
I understand.
However, I'd like to make a request.
You two will participate in a mock battle
today.
I want to see all the skill and power
you've gained.
Do not go easy on each other.
Fight with the intent to kill.
Hinata, you're the successor of the Hyuga
clan.
This is your chance to show me you're
worthy.
Yes, sir.
But... I'm supposed to fight.
Begin!
Let's do this!
Elder sister, Hinata...
Both of them are amazing!
There's no end to this.
There!
Stop!
Falling to Hanabi who's five years
younger!
Enough!
Just go!
Hinata will probably just serve the
village as a genin.
Oh, I see.
It seems sad, but we cannot allow a
failure like that to become our successor.
This is her destiny.
That you were born
possessing strength surpassing
that of your elder
sister is also destiny.
Hanabi, you must hone your skills to the
utmost for the sake of the Hyuga.
Yes.
Stand up, Hanabi.
I will take Hinata under my wing.
But are you... are you sure that's what
you want?
She is your firstborn and heir to your
household.
The life of a genin can be dangerous and
brief.
Do whatever you will.
She's of less worth than her sister,
five years her junior.
The Hyuga clan has no use for such an
heir.
Father has turned his back on elder
sister.
If you have nothing more to say,
leave us now.
We have work to do.
All right.
Continue, Hanabi!
Yes.
If elder sister can't do it, I have no
choice but to do it.
I will protect the Hyuga.
This is my destiny.
You know, sometimes I wonder if he'll be
okay.
I'm worried that he's just too scared.
I mean, sure, he did
finally become a genin,
but he always shies
away from confrontation.
Soon he'll be sent out on missions and may
have to face foes in life or death battles.
And as it is, well, to put
it bluntly, I fear that Choji
will be killed because he's
too scared to make a move.
Frankly, I seriously doubt that he's ever
going to become a chunin.
You're off base about him, Choza.
Your son is not a coward.
He's simply kind.
Maybe, but in the shinobi world,
that's the same thing.
Then I say let him be who he is.
Let him be kind.
Are you serious?
Be kind?
Yes.
The kindness that he possesses is a unique
weapon that he, and only he, has.
A weapon?
He's just a boy.
It can't be helped if his kindness is seen
as cowardice.
But someday, his kindness will be a thing
of greatness.
The time will come
when the Hidden Leaf will
need the kindness that
he brings to the world.
However, he's also going to need to have
strength that can rival that kindness.
He needs to have the intensity to
recognize, feel, and accept others' pain.
Or even reject it, but still envelop them
in his kindness.
I know that boy has those qualities.
Asuma...
Choza is going to experience many things,
both good and bad.
This is the shinobi world, after all,
so he'll have to face many hardships.
But with each experience he has,
he will grow stronger and kinder.
Asuma won't be the only one.
Huh?
Today's the day, so...
Let's chow down.
Sakura, isn't it time for you to get
going?
I know!
I'm on my way out now!
How long are you going to treat me like a
kid?
I'm a ninja now!
So... I'm not a little academy student
anymore.
I'm Sakura Haruno.
Kunoichi in training.
See you later!
Good morning, Sakura.
Good morning, Ino.
So they actually let you graduate?
What a surprise.
Those classes are ancient history.
We're both ninja now and we're both equal.
I won't lose to you anymore.
So!
What are you doing here, Naruto?
This isn't for dropouts.
You can't be here unless you graduate.
Oh yeah?
Do you see this?
Open your eyes, Shikamaru.
It's a regulation headband.
We're going to be training together!
How do you like that?
Heh.
Let me put it to you this way.
I look great in this headgear.
Like it was made for me.
Believe it!
Naruto, you graduated after all.
I'm glad.
I'm first!
I won again, Sakura.
Give it up.
I had to look back to see you.
My toe was at least a tenth of an inch
ahead.
Have you always been this delusional?
Sakura...
She's smiling at me.
I think she likes me in this headband.
Hey, whoa!
Where are you going?
Hi, Sakura.
What's up?
Move it!
Good morning, Sasuke.
Mind if I sit next to you?
Back off, forehead!
I'm sitting next to Sasuke.
I was here first.
I walked into the classroom before you
did.
Everybody saw it.
Dream on.
Actually, I got here before either of you.
So did I.
I'm sitting next to Sasuke.
No, I am!
Clueless.
Naruto!
He stopped glaring at Sasuke!
Sakura?
Why are they so obsessed with him?
Sasuke!
What's the big deal with this guy?
Don't let him have it!
You are going to get stuck in the future?
Of course, Sasuke!
We will!
Wow!
Haha!
This is great!
Sorry, did I bump you?
What the...
I, uhh... I, uhh...
I, uh... Uaah!
Uaah!
Shou!
This is outrageous!
I was supposed to be Sasuke's first kiss!
Naruto will pay for this!
Shou!
I'll get you, Naruto!
They are vicious!
Danger!
Naruto, you are so dead!
Hey, whoa!
It was an accident!
You're finished!
Hold on!
As of today, you are all ninjas.
To get here, you've faced difficult trials
and hardships.
But that's nothing.
What comes next will be far more
difficult.
Now you are only Genin, first-level
ninjas.
All the Genin will be grouped into
three-man squads.
Each squad will be led by a Jonin,
an elite ninja.
We want each squad to
have a balance of strengths
and abilities, so that's
how we set them up.
I will now announce the squads.
Squad 7.
Naruto Uzumaki.
Sakura Haruno.
Yay!
I'm doomed.
And Sasuke Uchiha.
I won't be with Naruto, then.
Next, Squad 8.
Hinata Yuga.
Yes, sir.
Kiba Inuzuka.
Shino Aburame.
How did you get in his group?
Ka-ching!
True love conquers all!
I don't get it.
What do you see in a guy like that?
He's not so special.
You are so beyond clueless, Shikamaru.
Don't you get it?
No, I don't get it, because I'm not a
girl.
You are so full of yourself.
Jealousy is a terrible thing.
I'd hate to be on your squad.
Now, Squad 10.
Ino Yamanaka.
Shikamaru Nara.
Did you say something about hating to be
on my squad?
And Choji Akimichi.
Not Food Boy, too!
Those are all the squads.
Iruka-sensei, why does
a great ninja like me have
to be in the same group
with a slug like Sasuke?
Sasuke had the best scores of all the
graduating students.
Naruto, you had the worst scores.
To create a balanced group, we put the
best student with the worst student.
Just make sure you don't get in my way,
loser.
Hey, what did you say?
Hard of hearing.
Knock it off, Naruto!
Sit down!
After lunch, you'll meet your new Jonin
teachers.
Until then, class dismissed.
What a pain.
I get into the same group as Sakura,
and he's gotta be in it, too.
There's got to be a way to deal with this.
Huh?
Got it!
Naruto!
Sit down!
Well, it's not like there's a big rush or
anything.
I'll be in the same group as Sasuke for a
long time.
But still...
How could I even think he'd like me?
Let's face it, I'm scrawny and small,
except for my forehead.
Why was I born with such a big,
wide forehead?
Sasuke... he's looking... right at me.
That look in his eyes...
Sakura, your forehead is so wide and
charming.
It makes me... feel like kissing it.
Well, there's lots of room up there.
I'm not a fairy tale, and fairy tales
don't come true.
Sakura, your forehead is so wide and
charming...
It makes me feel like kissing it.
Ka-ching!
She scores!
This fairy tale is for real!
Just kidding.
That's the kind of dumb thing that Naruto
would say.
Ugh...
I wanna ask you something.
Huh?
Naruto... what do you think of him?
He knows about my feelings, and he
purposely tries to get in the way.
He enjoys interfering and making me feel
bad.
Naruto... he doesn't understand one single
thing about me.
He's just annoying.
All I really want... is for you to accept
me, Sasuke.
That's all.
You just want me to accept you?
Yes, that's how I feel.
I'd do anything for that.
I let my guard down.
It's true.
I'm desperate.
I finally know why... why I like Sakura so
much.
I finally understand.
I found my stomach.
Ah!
My stomach!
What timing!
Ah!
Hey!
What's the matter?
I'll be right back!
I didn't know that Sasuke was so shy.
Maybe he needs a little time to get ready.
Ah!
Ah.
Close.
Really close.
My stomach was so upset, I almost lost
control of the jutsu.
Why did it have to happen right then?
Just when she was about to...
She thinks that I'm annoying?
She said that three times.
I transform into Sasuke, get close to
Sakura, and she has to say that?
Sasuke, you're back!
Don't be so shy, you bad boy!
Are you ready now?
You know, mentally prepared?
Because I am, I mean, I'm raring to go!
Hey, wait a minute!
Where's Naruto?
Oh, see, there you go, changing the
subject again.
Anyway, Naruto just picks fights with you.
You know why he's so annoying?
Because he wasn't raised right.
He doesn't have a mother or father,
no one to teach him right from wrong.
Think about it, he just does whatever
comes into his head.
If I did things like Naruto, forget it!
I mean, my parents would get mad and I'd
get in trouble, so of course I don't do it!
But if you don't have parents...
If you don't have parents to tell you,
how would you know?
He's selfish and bratty!
He's all alone!
Alone.
Isolated.
Huh?
It's not about your parents scolding you.
You have no idea what it means to be
alone.
Wh-why are you saying that?
Because you're annoying.
So this is where Naruto lives.
Yes, he'll be on your team, along with
Sakura and Sasuke from the Uchiha clan.
Good luck.
Yes, he'll be on your team, along with
Sakura and Sasuke from the Uchiha clan.
Good luck.
You'll need it.
This milk is way past its expiration date.
One sip of this and he'd be running to the
bathroom all day.
Seems like this kid's just one big
problem.
Naruto, just sit down!
I don't want to!
How come our teacher's the only one that's
late?
I don't want to!
How come our teacher's the only one that's
late?
Leave it!
The other group's already met
their new teachers and took off
on some adventure or something,
and Iruka-sensei's gone too.
We know, okay?
Hey, what are you doing?
Naruto!
That's what he gets for coming late.
Surprise!
You're asking for trouble.
You know you shouldn't do that.
I love stuff like this!
Hm.
Our teacher's a Jounin, an elite ninja.
You think he'd fall for that?
Yeah, Sasuke's right.
You're so clueless, Naruto.
I got him!
He totally fell for it!
I'm sorry, sensei.
I told him not to do it, but he wouldn't
listen.
I'd never do anything like that.
Perfect shot!
He actually fell for that cheap trick?
Is this guy really a Jounin?
Hm.
How can I put this?
My first impression of this group?
You're a bunch of idiots.
Alright, why don't you introduce
yourselves, one at a time?
Introduce ourselves?
Well, what are we supposed to say?
Things you like.
Things you hate.
Dreams for the future.
Hobbies.
Things like that.
Why don't you tell us stuff first?
I mean, before we talk, tell us about you
so we can see how it's supposed to work.
Me?
I'm Kakashi Hatake.
Things I like and things I hate.
I don't feel like telling you that.
Huh?
My dreams for the future.
Never really thought about it.
As for my hobbies... I have lots of
hobbies.
That was totally useless.
All he really told us was his name.
Okay, your turn.
You on the right.
You first.
Believe it.
I'm Naruto Uzumaki.
I like instant ramen in a cup.
And I really like the ramen Iruka-sensei
got me at the Ichiraku Noodle Shop.
But I hate the three
minutes you have to wait
after you pour the
water in the ramen cup.
My hobby is eating different kinds of
ramen and comparing them.
And my future dream is... to be the
greatest hokage!
Then the whole village
will stop disrespecting
me and start treating
me like I'm nothing.
I'm somebody!
Somebody important!
Well, he's grown up in a very interesting
way.
Alright, next.
I'm Sakura Haruno.
What I like, uh... I mean, the person I
like is...
Uh, my hobby is, uh...
My dream for the future is...
And?
What do you hate?
Naruto!
Last one.
My name... is Sasuke Uchiha.
I hate a lot of things.
And I don't particularly like anything.
What I have is not a dream.
Because I will make it a reality.
I'm going to restore my clan.
And destroy a certain someone.
Just as I thought.
Good.
You're each unique and you have your own
ideas.
We'll have our first mission tomorrow.
What kind of mission are we going to have?
A survival exercise.
Huh?
Survival exercise?
We already did this stuff at the academy.
That's how we got here.
This is not like your previous training.
So, uh... so, uh... what kind of training
is it, then?
Hehehehehehehehehehe.
Hey, hold on.
That's a normal question.
What's so funny?
Well, if I tell you the answer,
you're not going to like it.
Huh?
Of the 27 graduates who just came here,
only 9 will actually be accepted as Genin.
The other 18 will be weeded out and sent
back to the academy.
In other words, this is a
make-it-or-break-it pass-fail test.
And the chance that you'll fail is at
least 66%.
See?
Didn't I tell you you wouldn't like it?
That's crazy!
We worked hard to get here!
Believe it!
What was that graduation test for,
anyway?
Oh, that?
That was just to select candidates who
might become Genin.
Or not.
What?!
That's how it is.
I decide whether you pass or fail.
Be at the designated training spot at 5 AM
and bring your ninja gear.
Well, I'm not going to be weeded out!
People are going to look up to me someday!
I've got to pass this test!
Believe it!
If I fail, I'll be separated from Sasuke!
This is a trial of love!
That's it.
You're dismissed.
Oh.
Tomorrow you better skip breakfast or
else... you'll puke.
Marvelous.
Go-go, Sasuke!
Morning, everyone.
Ready for your first day?
Hey, you're late!
Well, a black cat crossed my path,
so I had to take the long way.
Well, let's get started.
Here we go.
It's set for noon.
Your assignment is very simple.
You just have to take these bells from me.
That's all there is to it.
If you can't get them by noon,
you go without lunch.
You'll be tied to those posts and you'll
watch while I eat my lunch in front of you.
So that's why.
He told us not to eat breakfast to make it
harder on us.
Wait a minute, there's three of us.
How come there's only two bells?
Well, that way, at least one of you will
end up tied to a post and ultimately
disqualified for failing to complete the
mission.
That one goes back to the Academy.
Then again, all three of you could flunk
out, too.
You can use any weapons, including
shuriken, if you're not prepared to get hit.
If you kill me, you won't be able to take
the bells.
Those weapons are too dangerous,
Sensei!
Especially since you couldn't even dodge
that eraser.
Class clowns are usually the weakest
links.
You can safely ignore them.
Lowest scores, losers.
When I say start, you can begin.
Losers, losers, losers.
Don't be in such a hurry.
I didn't say start yet.
He's so fast!
I didn't even see it.
So this is it, Joninne...
But you came at me with the full intention
of destroying me, so...
how can I say this... I'm actually
starting to like you guys.
Start!
Ninja must know how to conceal their
trust.
You and me!
Right now!
Fair and square!
Let's go!
Fool.
You know, compared to the others,
you're a little bit... weird.
Oh yeah?
The only thing weird here is your haircut.
Ah!
Hmm...
Shinobi Battle Techniques.
Part 1.
Taijutsu.
The physical art.
Ah!
Taijutsu!
That's hand-to-hand combat!
Then why is he reaching for a weapon?
What the...
What are you waiting for?
Make your move.
But, I mean, why are you reading that
book?
Why?
To find out what happens in the story,
of course.
Don't let it bother you.
With your weak attacks, it doesn't really
matter if I'm reading or whatever.
I'm going to crush you!
Now you're mine!
Don't let your enemy get behind you all
the time.
A hand sign to focus his chakra.
Is that the sign of the tiger?
That's dangerous.
He could destroy Naruto with that.
That hand sign is for a fire jutsu.
He's not just toying with Naruto.
He's going to demolish him.
Naruto!
Get out of there, quick!
He's going to destroy you!
Leaf Village Secret Finger Jutsu!
A thousand years of death!
That wasn't a hand sign at all.
He just poked him.
Tuna!
Those two are just total idiots.
Okay, where was I?
That must be against the rules.
He's a Jonin.
We can't possibly match his strength.
I'm not going to let it end like this.
I'll attack from the water.
Now!
What are you doing now?
You know you won't get lunch unless you
take a bell by noon.
I'll find the strength somehow.
Believe it!
I'm going to pass this test, and I'm not
going back to the academy.
I will become a ninja!
Hmm... I'm going
to get you, Master.
You're overconfident, Sensei!
That's why you weren't ready for a Shadow
Clone attack by Best Jutsu!
Seven Naruto's?
What?
They're not images.
They're real!
How could he do that?
Hmm...
It looks like the stories are true.
He can create Shadow Clones.
Great technique, but I don't think you can
maintain it for very long.
You talk like you're the best, Naruto,
but you're still the worst student.
What?
He got me from behind!
Hahahaha!
Didn't you say don't let your enemies get
behind you?
Good advice, Sensei!
Believe it!
I had one of my clones come out of the
river, then sneak up behind me, super quiet!
Now this is for nailing me in the butt
earlier!
When did Naruto get so cool?
A diversionary tactic.
Nice.
Aaaaaah!
You're mine, and so are those bells!
Ugh!
Aaaaah!
Huh?
Ouch!
It's you!
You're Kakashi Sensei, aren't you?
You transformed into me using a jutsu!
You are Kakashi Sensei!
You smell like an old man!
You must be him!
No, you are!
No, you're Kakashi Sensei!
Hey!
Let's undo the jutsu!
Yeah!
That's it!
Believe it!
Then there'll be just two of us!
I don't know who's who!
Should've thought of that sooner,
fool!
You're the jerk!
Why didn't you think of it?
Just undo the jutsu!
Ugh...
Naruto, you are so not cool.
He got you with a replacement jutsu,
loser.
With this jutsu, you quickly switch your
own body with an object, so your enemy
thinks he's attacking you, when he's
actually attacking a log or rock.
He made Naruto look like a total moron.
Huh?
A bell?
I must've got to him with my attack!
He dropped a bell!
Hey!
Let me down!
What is this?
Of course it was a trap.
Help me!
That Jounin doesn't let down his guard,
even when he's fighting a fool like Naruto.
Come on!
Think before you use a jutsu, or else your
opponent might use it against you.
Oh, and also, if the bait is obvious,
don't take it.
A ninja must see through deception.
I... get... it!
Ah!
I'm telling you this because you don't get
it.
You think you get it, which is not the
same as actually getting it.
Get it?
This is my chance!
He finally dropped his guard!
Won't you ever learn.
He just got blasted by Shuriken!
Are you out of your mind, Sasuke?
You went too far!
You've failed me.
But if you'll stop me, Where's my sensei?
I need to talk to him.
I can't...
I can't hear you, Sasuke.
I'm going to be fine.
A ninja must see through deception.
Yeah, yeah!
How am I supposed to do that?
Well, I'm sure not falling for any more of
his traps!
I fell for it again!
Oh
my!
Someone there.
I think I felt something.
What was it?
What's going on?
Sakura... Sasuke!
S-Sakura!
Help me!
Please help me!
I think I overdid it a bit.
Hm?
Sounded like... Sakura?
Shinobi battle skill number two,
the illusion jutsu.
Sakura studied it in class, but she still
couldn't see it coming.
Kenjutsu.
It's just simple mind control.
I'm not surprised he caught Sakura with
it, but... I'm not like Sakura and Naruto.
Say that after you get one of these.
My Sasuke...
There's no point using normal attacks!
A trap!
This kid.
..
He's fierce.
Hm.
I won't be able to read Make Out Paradise
now.
What... What happened?
Sasuke!
I saw him!
He was on the verge of... No!
Sasuke, no!
You've got to survive, please!
Where are you?
Hmm... Hmm...
Huh?
Hey!
What are those things down there?
Ah!
I know what those things are!
Those are boxed lunches!
Oh... A ninja must see through deception!
Well, you are different from the other
two, I'll grant you that.
Hmph.
Horse!
Tiger!
Fire style!
Fireball jutsu!
What?
Genin can't do fire jutsu.
Takes too much chakra.
There's no way.
Where did he go?
Behind me?
Above?
Right under your feet.
Earth style.
Headhunter jutsu.
Can't move, huh?
That was ninjutsu, the third shinobi
battle skill.
You have talent, and you were right.
You are... different from the others.
But different isn't always better.
They say the nail that sticks up is the
one that gets hammered down.
Sensei told us that if we don't get a
bell, then we don't get any lunch.
But if I eat my lunch now, then there's
nothing he can do!
It's Chao time!
Hi there.
Aaaaaaah!
I was just joking, Sensei.
Nice try.
He's stronger than I am.
I can't get around that.
Sakura?
Sasuke's just a hand without a body and
he's talking!
And that's my partner.
Sasuke...
You're okay!
Hey, cut it out!
Let go!
I've got to get a bell before lunch.
That doesn't leave much time.
Sasuke, you're still trying to get one of
those bells?
A while ago, I touched one.
Next time, I'll get one.
That is really great.
I can't believe you did that.
You're amazing!
I can't believe it!
He touched one of the bells!
I'll never get my hands on one of those
things!
Which means Sasuke will pass and I won't!
And we'll be separated forever!
No, no, no, no, no!
Uh, it's almost lunch.
There's not really enough time left,
so maybe we should just give up.
And then try again next year.
All right.
Mm-hmm.
I'm the only one who can destroy that
person.
What?
Who?
You mean the sensei?
That day, I was crying.
When were you crying?
It was my...
What?
What happened to you?
I am an Avenger.
That means I must be stronger than my
prey.
I need this training.
There's no time for setbacks.
I wasted too much time.
Uh-oh.
Stomach's growling, huh?
That's too bad.
Oh, by the way, about this exercise...
Well, I've decided.
I won't send any of you back to the
Academy.
Yes, all three of you are being dropped
from the program.
Permanently.
Iruka, what did you wish to see me about?
I don't think you came here merely to
drink tea with me and chat, did you?
Naruto's been assigned to Squad Seven.
The Jonin in charge of that group.
Just how tough a trainer is he?
Kakashi, you mean.
You are concerned about him.
I am.
I heard a rumor about his training
methods.
Hmm...
What's this?
All the trainees who've ever been assigned
to him.
Those who passed and those who failed.
May I?
Huh?
This?
This is... Drop us
from the program?
That means we can never become ninja.
You said if we couldn't take the bells,
we'd be sent back to the Academy.
You can't just change your mind and kick
us out.
Why would you do that?
Because you don't think like ninja.
You think like little kids.
Like brats.
Satsuki!
You think it's all about you.
Let go, Sasuke!
You can't step on him like he's some bug!
Use your head.
Three people on a squad.
Why do you think we would do that?
Ah!
How are we supposed to know why you picked
three people?
We didn't make the rules!
It's so basic.
Teamwork.
If all three of you had come at me,
you might have been able to take them.
Well, anyway, it's over.
Wait a minute... You set it up with
three people, but only two bells.
If we worked together and got the bells,
only two of us could keep them,
and that would lead to group conflict and
the squad would break up.
Exactly.
I purposely pitted you against each other.
Huh?
I wanted to see if you could overcome that
and put the squad ahead of yourselves.
A genin should have a
natural feel for teamwork,
but you... it never
even crossed your mind.
Sakura, you obsessed about Sasuke,
who was gone, while Naruto was right in
front of you and you wouldn't lift a
finger to help him.
Naruto, you do everything on your own.
Everything.
And you, Sasuke, thought the others were
so far beneath you they were worthless.
Arrogance.
Ninja missions are carried out in squads.
Of course, you need individual skills, but
teamwork is the most essential element.
Every shinobi understands this.
When individuals put themselves above the
squad, this can lead to failure and death.
For example... Sakura, kill
Naruto now or Sasuke dies.
That's what happens on a mission.
The enemy takes a hostage and you've got
an enemy.
It's an impossible choice, and someone
ends up dead.
On every mission, your life is on the
line.
Did you look at this stone?
The names engraved on it?
They are all ninja who are honored as
heroes in our village.
That's it!
Now I know!
I've decided I'm gonna have my name
engraved on that stone!
I'm not gonna live and die for nothing
like a dog!
I'm gonna be a hero!
A hero!
They are... a special kind of hero.
Huh?
What kind of heroes are they?
Come on, tell us!
Well, well...
They're all K.I.A.
This is a memorial stone.
The names of my closest friends are
engraved here.
My son!
Please tell me this was me who was raised
as a hero Alright, I'm going to give you
one more chance, but
I'm going to make it much
harder on you you have
three hours to get a bell.
Eat lunch now to build up strength but
Naruto doesn't get any.
It's your punishment for breaking the
rules and trying to eat by yourself.
And if anyone tries to feed him,
that person will immediately fail.
I make the rules.
You follow them.
Got it?
Here.
What?
No, Sasuke, you can't do that!
You heard what the sensei said!
Kakashi's gone.
We need to get those bells as a team.
If Naruto's hungry, he'll be weak and
ineffective.
That hurts the team and jeopardizes the
mission.
Um... Sasuke...
It can't be.
This is even worse than the rumors.
Kakashi is dead.
This may be a bit more difficult than the
others.
A bit more difficult?
Not a single student has ever passed his
test.
That's true.
They all tried, but not one of them could
live up to Kakashi's standards.
So they were all... eliminated.
You!
You
broke the rules.
I hope you're ready for the punishment.
Any last words?
You pass.
Huh?
What do you mean?
How'd we pass?
You're the first squad that ever
succeeded.
The others did exactly what I said,
and fell into every trap.
They couldn't think for themselves.
A ninja must see through deception.
In the ninja world, those who break the
rules are scum.
That's true.
But... those who abandon their friends...
are worse than scum.
Hmm...
He's, uh... you know... he's kinda cool.
The exercise is over.
Everyone passes.
Squad 7 starts its first mission tomorrow.
Yes!
I get it!
Believe it!
I'm a ninja!
Ninja!
Let's go home.
Show some love, and I'll make our during
the night.
I knew they'd do this!
It happens every time.
Believe it!
You guys forgot to untie me!
Oh no...
I know this is too much for theyard.
Before you idealize, motivate your anger.
Make them all realize.
Climb in the mountain.
Never coming down.
Break into the contents.
Never falling down.
My knee is still shaking.
Like I was twelve.
Sneaking out the classroom.
By the back door.
A moral let me try some.
But I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting.
For people like me.
Don't try to look so wise Don't cry cause
you look so right.
Don't try to make some fears.
Cause you were Turtle in the end.
Don't try to look so wise Don't cry cause
you look so right.
Thank you for watching!